Never bet against a man with a killer hand.
Wild Card is a thriller, crime, action film directed by Simon West.
When a Las Vegas bodyguard with lethal skills and a gambling problem gets in
trouble with the mob, he has one last play… and it's all or nothing.
Nick Wild, played by Jason Statham.
Cyrus Kinnick, played by Michael Angarano.
Holly, played by Dominik Garcia.
Danny DeMarco, played by Milo Ventimiglia.
Cassandra, played by Hope Davis.
Osgood, played by Max Casella.
Wild Card is a 2015 American action thriller film directed by Simon West and starring Jason Statham,
Michael Angarano, Milo Ventimiglia, Dominik Garcia-Lorido, Anne Heche, and Sofia Vergara.
Based on the 1985 novel Heat by William Goldman, it is a remake of
the 1986 adaptation that starred Burt Reynolds.
The film was released in the United States on January 30, 2015 in
a limited release and through video on demand.
Wild Card received negative reviews and was a box-office bomb, making
only $6.7 million worldwide against a $30 million budget.
The film explores themes of gambling, bodyguard, remake, las vegas.
The tone is intense.